miraistore.com 2013-05-12

# Our Privacy Policy | MiraiStore.com

1\. GENERAL PRINCIPLES

We value the trust you place with miraistore.com. Protecting your privacy is very important to us, which is why we insist upon highest of standards and follow the most stringent procedures to help protect the confidential information that is stored on our systems. We have committed ourselves to do everything we reasonably can to protect your rights of privacy on the systems and the Website controlled by us. However, please be informed that we are not liable for any unauthorised or unlawful disclosures of your personal and confidential information made by third parties who are not subject to our control, for example advertisers and websites that have links to our Website.. You should take note that the information and privacy practices of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors or other sites to which we provide hyperlinks, may be different from ours. Please read the following to learn more about our information gathering and dissemination practices.

**We categorise information about you (collectively referred to as "Personal Information") as follows:**

**(a) Profiling Information:**  With a view to provide you the best shopping experience, we keep a track of your Personal Information. In general, you can browse our Website without telling us who you are or revealing any of your personal information. It is only when you register (login) and supply your email address and a password, will you be providing us your personal information. This allows us an access to your account every time you visit our Website. Information which you provide when you register for a Service may include some or all of the following:-

i. Information about your personal identity such as gender, marital status, age, preferences, likes and dislikes etc;

ii. Your financial information such as your banking details and any such information relating to your income and lifestyle levels;

iii. Your contact details such as your physical addresses, postal addresses, telephone and fax numbers and the like, and  

iv. In the case of Facebook aligned services (if so opted by you), publicly available information of your friends, their likes and dislikes, etc. 

**(b) Payment and Account Information:**  We will maintain your account history with us which shall include (but not be limited to) all billing information and communications, payment history etc. All such information is maintained in encrypted forms on secure servers. 

**(c) Service Usage:**  All such information about your navigation using our Services, for example the URLs of websites, which you visit and from which you request downloads. 

**(d) Log information:** **All such** information involving your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, date and time of request. 

**(e) Transactional Information:**  Transactional history (other than banking details) about your e-commerce activities. 

**(f) Correspondence Information:** Information about your correspondents, and the destination/origin of communications between you and any other person using our Services, which may include email communications, blog, chat room and discussion board communications, instant message communications, experts forum communications, fax mail communications, membership of mailing lists etc. 

**(g) User IDs:**  Your usernames, passwords, email addresses and other security-related information provided by you in relation to our Services. 

**(h) Stored Information:**  Data either created by you or by a third party and which you wish to store on our servers such as image files, documents etc. 

**The Personal Information collected by us is only with a view to conduct our business and to enable us to deliver and improve our Services to you. We do not for any reason sell your Personal Information to any third party or otherwise trade on it.** We will only disclose your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Any of your information which is provided by you while using certain Services are open to any public environment or forum including (but not limited to) any blog, community or discussion board, shall not be dealt as confidential, and is not subject to protection under Privacy Policy. You will be solely responsible for any information shared by you in such public forums. Information, which is disclosed publicly, is also shared with our affiliates, third party service providers, sponsors of competitions etc. unless expressly stated otherwise. We are not liable to you or any third party for any damage that you or any third party may suffer howsoever arising from your disclosure of Personal Information in any public forum. 

2\. RIGHT TO COLLECT

We use personal information to provide the services you request, and only to the extent to market such services to you. By accepting the Terms of Service you agree that we may collect and store your Personal Information as long as you use our Services subject to the limitations set out in this Privacy Policy.

 We collect and store your Service Usage and Transactional Information to:  **(a)** To administer our relationship with you. **(b)**  Comply with any statutory or regulatory requirement.  **(c)**  Compile statistical and demographical profiles about you for our business and marketing activities and to customize our Services to you. We are entitled to use such information about you for our own internal business purposes, and in such cases we will only disclose it in a very discreet manner and in a way in which it is not capable of being used or interpreted in such a manner as to identify you; and  **(d)**  monitor your use of our Services for the purposes of ensuring compliance with our Terms and Conditions.

Any monitoring by us may include (but not be limited to) the filtering of incoming and outgoing electronic data messages to identify, limit and/or prevent the transmission of spam, viruses and/or unlawful, defamatory, obscene or otherwise undesirable material or content.

COOKIES

A "cookie" is a small piece of information stored by a Web server on a Web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. We use "cookies" so that we can provide you with more customised information when you return to our website. "Cookies" are used to store user preferences and to track user trends, so as to enhance your interactive experience and generally improve our Services to you. You can set your browser to notify you when you are sent a "cookie", giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. If you do accept a "cookie", you thereby agree that we may use of any Personal Information collected by us using that cookie. You may update your Profiling Information at any time on the website. You acknowledge and agree that in the interests of improving personalisation and Service efficiency, we may, under controlled and secure circumstances, share your Personal Information with our affiliates (an entity which is our subsidiary or holding company or a subsidiary of our holding company or an entity which controls, is controlled by or is under common control with us).

3\. GENERAL EXCEPTIONS

If we are required to intercept, disclose, monitor and/or store your Personal Information we may do so only in the following situations:   **(a)**  mandate of law;  **(b)** to conduct our business;  **(c)**  to secure our systems; or  **(d)**  to enforce our own rights. However, any such disclosure shall be in accordance with the procedure prescribed by law.

There may be such situations wherein interception, disclosure, monitoring and storage may take place without your knowledge. In that case, we will not be liable to you or any third party for any damages howsoever arising from such interception, disclosure, monitoring and storage..

There are instances where we use various outside agencies (third party service providers) to make our Website operate. Such third parties may need access to your information in order to make the services provided through our Website work. Information will only be disclosed to these service providers on a need-to-know basis, and they will only be permitted to use such information for the purpose of providing the particular services provided by such entities in connection with our Website.

4\. CHANGES IN POLICY

By using this Website and by providing your information, you acknowledge your assent to our Privacy Policy. If you do not want to be bound by the terms kindly restrain yourself from subscribing to or using our Services. Your access to and usage of the Website and any dispute over privacy are subject to this policy and our Terms and Conditions, including limitations on damages. We also reserve the right to change the Privacy Policy, at any time. We will post any changes so that you are always aware of our policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.

**5.** GRIEVANCE OFFICER 

In accordance with Information Technology Act 2000 and rules made there under, the name and contact details of the Grievance Officer are provided below:

**Mr. Kumar**  
 **Uniworld Lifestyle Pvt. Limited**  
#225, S.T Bed Extn, 5th Main,  
4th Block, Koramangala  
Bangalore - 560034  
Phone: 080-4012 4212  
Email: [grievances@miraistore.com](mailto:grievances@miraistore.com)   
Time: Mon-Fri (10:00 – 18:00 hrs)
